<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quotes</string>



    <string-array name= "quotes">

        <item>Laugh and the world laughs with you, snore and you
 sleep alone. Anthony Burgess</item>

<item>A successful man is one who makes more money than his
 wife can spend. A successful woman is one who can
 find such a man.  Lana Turner </item>

<item>Roses are red, violets are blue, Im schizophrenic,
 and so am I.
  Oscar Levant </item>

<item>A womans mind is cleaner than a mans: She changes it
 more often.   Oliver Herford </item>

<item>Behind every great man is a woman rolling her eyes.
 Jim Carrey </item>

<item>People who think they know everything are a great
 annoyance to those of us who do.  Isaac Asimov </item>

<item>The universe is a big place, perhaps the biggest.
  Kurt Vonnegut </item>

<item>Conscience is a mother.in.law whose visit never ends.
 H. L. Mencken </item>

<item>Legend A lie that has attained the dignity of age.
  H. L. Mencken </item>

<item> The only really happy folk are married women and single men.
  H. L. Mencken</item>

<item>There is always an easy solution to every problem - neat,
 plausible, and wrong.  H. L. Mencken </item>

<item>Marriage is a wonderful institution, but who would want to
 live in an institution?  H. L. Mencken </item>

<item>Strike an average between what a woman thinks of her husband
 a month before she marries him and what she thinks of him a
 year afterward, and you will have the truth about him.
  H. L. Mencken </item>

<item>An idealist is one who, on noticing that a rose smells better
 than a cabbage, concludes that it will also make better
 soup. H. L. Mencken </item>

<item>A cynic is a man who, when he smells flowers, looks around
 for a coffin. H. L. Mencken </item>

<item>Marge: Now, I know you havent liked some of my past
       suggestions, like switching to the metric system
Abe: The metric system is the tool of the devil! My car
     gets forty rods to the hogshead and thats the way
     I likes it.
  The Simpsons episode A Star is Burns </item>

<item>Lets be very honest about what this is about. Its not about
 bashing Democrats, its not about taxes, they have no idea what
 the Boston tea party was about, they dont know their history
 at all. This is about hating a black man in the White House.
 This is racism straight up. Janeane Garofalo </item>

<item>If Barbie is so popular, why do you have to buy her
 friends?  Steven Wright </item>

<item>We can repair anything. (Please knock hard on the door -
 the bell doesnt work.
  Sign on door of repair shop </item>

<item>A verbal contract is not worth the paper its written on.  Samuel Goldwyn </item>

<item>Facts are stupid things.
 Ronald Reagan, Former U.S. President </item>





    </string-array>
</resources>
